

CALVIN LEONARDI

WEB & ANDROID DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

A certified experience from Dicoding Academy in the field of Web Development and Android for approximately 3 years. With this expertise, so I try to take advantage to work in the IT field especially the Web or Android development.

CONTACT

- Wonorejo Permai Timur IX / 9 Surabaya, Indonesia
- calvin_agus@yahoo.co.id
- 0878-5364-3183
- in <u>/calvinleonardi</u>

EDUCATION

SMAK Petra 5 (2013-2016) Sarjana Teknik Informatika di iSTTS (2016-2020)

SKILLS

- Programming (C#, Java, Codeigniter, Dart)
- Front-End (PHP, Javascript)
- Android & Flutter
- Database (MySQL, Firebase Realtime Database)
- Eager to learn something new
- Responsible for completing assignments on time

DICODING CERTIFICATION

- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula
- Belajar Membangun LINE Front-end Framework
- Belajar Dasar-Dasar Azure Cloud
- Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi Android
- Sertifikat Kelulusan Belajar Dasar-Dasar Azure Cloud
- Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)
- and more on my Linkedin

ORGANIZATION

Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa

DES 2016 - DES 2017

Manage Inventory and Needs at the BEM Office

Google Developer Group

NOV 2016 - NOV 2019

 Taking care of registration at the event held by the Surabaya GDG

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP

JAN 2018 - FEB 2018

• Help in the Front-end field - Zanette Software House

ANDROID DEVELOPER

JAN 2019 - JULY 2019

 Creating Academic Calendar for Campus - Institut Sains dan Teknologi Terpadu Surabaya